Angels from the realms of glory,
Wing your flight o`er all the earth;
Ye, who sang creation`s story,
Now proclaim Messiah`s birth;
Come and worship, Come and worship,
Worship Christ, the newborn King.
Shepherds, in the field abiding,
Watching o`er your flocks by night,
God with man is now residing;
Yonder shines the Infant Light;
Come and worship, Come and worship,
Worship Christ, the newborn King.
Sages, leave your contemplations,
Brighter visions beam afar;
Seek the great Desire of nations;
Ye have seen His natal star;
Come and worship, Come and worship,
Worship Christ, the newborn King.
Saints, before the altar bending,
Watching long in hope and fear,
Suddenly the Lord, descending,
In His temple shall appear;
Come and worship, Come and worship,
Worship Christ, the newborn King.