O Jesus sweet, O Jesus mild,
Thy Father’s will hast Thou fulfilled;
For Thou hast left Thy heavenly throne
Our lowly state to make Thine own.
O Jesus sweet, O Jesus mild.
O Jesus sweet, O Jesus mild,
With joy hast Thou the whole world filled;
Thou comest down from heaven’s hall
To comfort us whom tears enthrall.
O Jesus sweet, O Jesus mild.
O Jesus sweet, O Jesus mild,
Thou art love’s image undefiled.
Inflame our hearts with love’s pure fire,
That we may share Thy heart’s desire.
O Jesus sweet, O Jesus mild.
O Jesus sweet, O Jesus mild,
Help us to do as Thou hast willed.
What’er we have belongs to Thee:
O may we ever faithful be.
O Jesus sweet, O Jesus mild.