Songs of thankfulness and praise,
Jesus, Lord, to You we raise,
Manifested by the star
To the sages from afar;
Branch of royal David’s stem
In Your birth at Bethlehem;
Anthems be to You addressed,
God in man made manifest.
Manifest at Jordan’s stream,
Prophet, Priest, and King supreme;
And at Cana, wedding guest,
In Your Godhead manifest;
Manifest in power divine,
Changing water into wine;
Anthems be to You addressed,
God in man made manifest.
Manifest in making whole
Palsied limbs and fainting soul;
Manifest in valiant fight,
Quelling all the devil’s might;
Manifest in gracious will,
Ever bringing good from ill;
Anthems be to You addressed,
God in man made manifest.
Grant us grace to see You, Lord,
Mirrored in Your holy Word;
May we imitate Your way,
And be pure, as pure as we may,
That we like You may be
At Your great epiphany;
Let us praise You, ever blest,
God in man made manifest.