Thine is the glory,
Risen, conquering Son;
Endless is the victory thou o’er death hast won.
Angels in bright raiment rolled the stone away,
Kept the folded grave-clothes where Thy body lay.
Thine is the glory,
Risen, conquering Son;
Endless is the victory Thou o’er death hast won.
Lo! Jesus meets us.
Risen from the tomb,
Lovingly He greets us,
Scatters fear and gloom;
Let His Church with gladness hymns of triumph sing,
For her Lord now liveth;
Death has lost its sting.
No more we doubt Thee,
Glorious Prince of life!
Life is nought without Thee;
Aid us in our strife;
Make us more than conquerors through Thy deathless love
Bring us safe through Jordan to Thy home above.