Now the green blade rises from the buried grain,
What that in dark earth many days has lain;
Love lives again, that with the dead has been;
Love is come again like wheat arising green.
In the grave they laid Him, love by hatred slain,
Thinking that He would never wake again,
Laid in the earth like grain that sleeps unseen;
Love is come again like wheat arising green.
Forth He came in triumph, like the risen grain,
He that for three days in the grave had lain;
Raised from the dead, my living Lord is seen;
Love is come again like wheat arising green.
When our hearts are wintry, grieving, or in pain,
Your touch can call us back to life again,
Field of our hearts that dead and bare have been;
Love is come again like wheat arising green.