Hail the day that sees Him rise, Alleluia!
Glorious to His native skies; Alleluia!
Christ, awhile to mortals giv地, Alleluia!
Enters now the highest heav地! Alleluia!
There the glorious triumph waits; Alleluia!
Lift your heads, eternal gates! Alleluia!
Wide unfold the radiant scene; Alleluia!
Take the King of glory in! Alleluia!
See! He lifts His hands above; Alleluia!
See! He shows the prints of love: Alleluia!
Hark! His gracious lips bestow, Alleluia!
Blessings on His Church below. Alleluia!
Lord beyond our mortal sight, Alleluia!
Raise our hearts to reach Thy height, Alleluia!
There Thy face unclouded see, Alleluia!
Find our heav地 of heav地s in Thee. Alleluia!