Jesus is all the world to me,
my life, my joy, my all;
he is my strength from day to day,
without him I would fall.
When I am sad, to him I go,
no other one can cheer me so;
when I am sad, he makes me glad,
he’s my friend.
Jesus is all the world to me,
my friend in trials sore;
I go to him for blessings, and
he gives them o’er and o’er.
He sends the sunshine and the rain,
he sends the harvest’s golden grain;
sunshine and rain, harvest of grain,
he’s my friend.
Jesus is all the world to me,
and true to him I’ll be;
O how could I this friend deny,
when he’s so true to me?
Following him I know I’m right,
he watches o’er me day and night;
following him by day and night,
he’s my friend.
Jesus is all the world to me,
I want no better friend;
I trust him now, I’ll trust him when
life’s fleeting days shall end.
Beautiful life with such a friend,
beautiful life that has no end;
eternal life, eternal joy,
he’s my friend.