I’ve found a Friend; oh, such a Friend!
He loved me ere I knew Him;
He drew me with the cords of love,
And thus He bound me to Him.
And ’round my heart still closely twine
Those ties which nought can sever,
For I am His, and He is mine,
Forever and forever.
I’ve found a Friend; oh, such a Friend!
He bled, He died to save me;
And not alone the gift of life,
But His own self He gave me.
Nought that I have my own I call,
I hold it for the Giver;
My heart, my strength, my life my all,
Are His, and His forever.
I’ve found a Friend; oh, such a Friend!
All power to Him is given;
To guard me on my upward course,
And bring me safe to heaven.
The eternal glories gleam afar,
To nerve my faint endeavor;
So now to watch, to work, to war,
And then to rest forever.
I’ve found a Friend; oh, such a Friend!
So kind, and true, and tender,
So wise a counselor and guide,
So mighty a defender.
From Him, who loveth me so well,
What power my soul can sever?
Shall life or death, or earth, or hell?
No; I am His forever.