O Shepherd divine, I know Thou art mine;
Thy search in the night was for me.
This bleak world is cold, but warm is Thy fold;
My Shepherd, I follow Thee.
Thy beautiful lamp shineth bright o’er my way,
Thy glorious light unto Thy perfect day.
Thro’ pastures serene,
Thro’ valleys of green,
My Shepherd, I follow Thee.
O Shepherd divine, I know Thou art mine;
Thy great heart was broken for me.
Thy grace and Thy law I picture in awe;
They kissed upon Calvary.
Ah! Life that was given to ransom my soul,
Ah! Heart that was broken to make sinners whole,
This world is but loss
In view of Thy cross,
My Shepherd, I follow Thee.
O Shepherd divine, I know Thou art mine;
I hear Thee say, “Follow thou Me.”
Thy message today illumines my way;
The Spirit of Prophecy.
I thrill at Thy marvellous love to Thy sheep,
The way Thou dost lead to the still waters deep,
One staff and one rod,
One fold and one God;
My Shepherd, I follow Thee.