Sing we of the modern city,
Scene alike of joy and stress;
Sing we of its nameless people
In their urban wilderness.
Into endless rows of houses
Life is set a millionfold,
Life expressed in human beings
Daily born and growing old.
In the city full of people,
World of speed and hectic days,
In the ever-changing setting
Of the latest trend and craze,
Christ is present, and among us;
In the crowd we see Him stand.
In the bustle of the city
Jesus Christ is every man.
God is not remote in heaven,
But on earth to share our shame,
Changing graph and mass and number
Into persons with a name.
Christ has shown, beyond statistics,
Human life with glory crowned,
By His timeless presence proving
People matter, people count!