O praise ye the Lord!
Praise Him in the height;
Rejoice in His word,
Ye angels of light;
Ye heavens, adore Him
By whom ye were made,
And worship before Him,
In brightness arrayed.
O praise ye the Lord!
Praise Him upon earth,
In tuneful accord:
Ye sons of new birth;
Praise Him who hath brought
you His grace from above,
Praise Him who hath taught
you To sing of His love.
O praise ye the Lord,
All things that give sound;
Each jubilant chord,
Re-echo around;
Loud organs His glory
Forth tell in deep tone,
And sweet harp, the story
Of what He hath done.
O praise ye the Lord!
Thanksgiving and song
To Him be outpoured
All ages along:
For love in creation,
For heaven restored.
For grace of salvation,
O praise ye the Lord!