When Jesus comes in glory,
As Lord and King of kings,
O what a wondrous story
The blessed Bible brings:
His face will shine like the sunlight,
His head be white as snow,
His eyes like flaming firelight,
His feet like brass aglow.
His voice like rushing waters
Will reach with mighty sound
Into the deepest quarters
Of all creation round;
And at this wondrous greeting
The dead in Christ shall rise,
Their Lord and Saviour meeting
In glory in the skies.
And we who believing
And His appearing love,
Shall know we are receiving
His glory from above;
His resurrection power
Will raise us to the place
Where we that wondrous hour
Shall see Him face to face.
O hasten Thine appearing
Thou bright and Morning Star!
Lord, may we soon be hearing
The trumpet sound afar;
They people all are yearning
To be Thy raptured bride,
To be Thy own returning
Be caught up to Thy side.