Rejoice, the Lord is King! Your Lord and King adore!
Rejoice, give thanks, and sing and triumph evermore
Lift up your heart, lift up your voice!
Rejoice, again I say, rejoice!
Jesus, the Savior, reigns, The God of truth and love;
When He had purged our stains, He took His seat above
Lift up your heart, lift up your voice!
Rejoice, again I say, rejoice!
His kingdom cannot fail, He rules o’er earth and heaven
The keys of death and grave Are to our Jesus given
Lift up your heart, lift up your voice!
Rejoice, again I say, rejoice!
Rejoice in glorious hope! Our Lord the judge shall come,
And take His servants up To their eternal home
Lift up your heart, lift up your voice!
Rejoice, again I say, rejoice!