Hark! ten thousand harps and voices
Sound the note of praise above;
Jesuse reigns, and heaven rejoices,
Jesus reigns, the God of love:
See, He sits on yonder throne;
Jesus rules the world alone.
Alleluia! Alleluia!
Alleluia! Amen.
King of glory, reign forever,
Thine an everlasting crown;
Nothing from Thy love shall sever
Those whom Thou hast made Thine own;
Happy objects of Thy grace,
Destined to behold Thy face.
Alleluia! Alleluia!
Alleluia! Amen.
Savior, hasten Thine appearing;
Bring, O bring the glorious day,
When, the awful summons hearing,
Heaven and earth shall pass away:;
Then, with golden harps we’ll sing,
“Glory, glory to our King!”
Alleluia! Alleluia!
Alleluia! Amen.