A hymn of glory let us sing;
New hymns thro’-out the world shall ring
Alleluia! Alleluia!
Christ, by a road before untrod,
Ascends unto the throne of God.
Alleluia! Alleluia!
Alleluia, alleluia, alleluia!
O Lord, our homeward pathway bend,
That our unwearied hearts ascend.
Alleluia! Alleluia!
Where, seated on Your Father’s throne,
You reign as King of kings alone.
Alleluia! Alleluia!
Alleluia, alleluia, alleluia!
Give us Your joy on earth, O Lord,
In heav’n to be our great reward.
Alleluia! Alleluia!
When throned with You forever, we
Shall praise Your name eternally.
Alleluia! Alleluia!
Alleluia, alleluia, alleluia!
O risen Christ, ascended Lord,
All praise to you let earth accord:
Alleluia! Alleluia!
You are, while endless ages run,
With Father and with Spirit one.
Alleluia! Alleluia!
Alleluia, alleluia, alleluia!