Now the joyful bells a-ring,
All ye mountains of the Lord!
Lift our hearts like birds a-winging,
All ye mountains, praise the Lord!
Now our festal season bringing
Kinsmen all to bide and board,
Sets our cheery voices singing;
All ye mountains, praise the Lord!
Dear our home as dear none other;
Where the mountains praise the Lord!
Gladly here our care we smother;
Here we know that Christ our brother
Binds us all as by a cord:
He was born of Mary mother
Where the mountains praise the Lord!
Cold the year, new whiteness wearing,
All ye mountains, praise the Lord!
Peace, good will to us a-bearing,
Now we all God’s goodness sharing
Break the bread and sheath the Sword:
Bright our hearths the signal flaring,
All ye mountains, praise the Lord!