I love Thee, I love Thee, I love Thee,my Lord;
I love Thee, my Savior, I love Thee, my God.
I love Thee, I love Thee, and that Thou dost know;
But how much I love Thee my actions will show.
I’m happy, I’m happy, O, wondrous account!
My joys are immortal, I stand on the mount!
I gaze on my treasure and long to be there,
With Jesus and angels, and kindred so dear.
O Jesus, my Savior, with Thee I am blest,
My life and salvation, my joy and my rest:
Thy name be my theme, and Thy love be my song;
Thy grace shall inspire both my heart and my tongue.
O, who’s like my Savior? He’s Salem’s bright King;
He smiles, and He loves me, and helps me to sing.
I’ll praise Him, I’ll praise Him, with notes loud and clear
While rivers of pleasure my spirit do cheer.