I serve a risen Savior,
He’s in the world today;
I know that He is living,
whatever men may say;
I see His hand of mercy,
I hear His voice of cheer
And just the time
I need Him He’s always near.
He lives, He lives,
Christ Jesus lives today!
He walks with me
and talks with me
along life’s narrow way.
He lives, He lives,
salvation to impart!
You ask me how I know He lives?
He lives within my heart.
In all the world around me
I see His loving care,
And tho’ my heart grows weary
I never will despair;
I know that He is leading
thru all the stormy blast,
The day of His appearing
will come at last.
Rejoice, rejoice, O Christian,
lift up your voice and sing,
Eternal hallelujahs
to Jesus Christ the King!
The hope of all who seek Him,
the help of all who find,
None other is so loving,
so good and kind.