Praise the Lord! you heavens, adore Him;
Praise Him, angels in the height;
Sun and moon, rejoice before Him,
Praise Him, all you stars of light.
Praise the Lord, for He has spoken;
World His mighty voice obeyed;
Laws which never shall be broken
For their guidance He has made.
Praise the Lord! for He is glorious;
Never shall HIs promise fail.
God has made His saints victorious;
Sin and death shall not prevail.
Praise the God of our salvation!
Hosts on high, His power proclaim;
Heaven and earth and all creation,
Laud and magnify His name.
Worship, honor, glory, blessing,
Lord, we offer as our gift.
Young and old, Your praise expressing,
Our glad songs to You we lift.
All the saints in heaven adore You,
We would join their glad acclaim;
As Your angels serve before You,
So on earth we praise Your name.