I have a Savior, He’s pleading in glory,
A dear, loving Savior, though earth friends be few;
And now He is watching in tenderness o’er me,
But oh that my Savior were your Savior, too.
For you I am praying, For you I am Praying,
For you am I praying, I’m praying for you.
I have a Father; to me He has given
A hope for eternity, blessed and true;
And soon He will call to meet Him in heaven,
But oh that He’d let me bring you with me, too!
I have a robe; ’tis resplendent in whiteness,
Awaiting in glory my wondering view;
Oh, when I receive it, all shining in brightness,
Dear friend, could I see you receiving one, too!
When Jesus has found you, tell others the story,
That my loving Savior is your Savior, too;
Then pray that your Savior will bring them to glory,
And prayer will be answered-’twas answered for you!