I am going to Calvary,
Would you like to come with Me
All the way and back again?
You must follow the Leader then.
You must follow the Leader,
All the way and back again,
You must follow the Leader.
If I want a thorny crown,
If the soldiers knock me down
Can I really be a king?
Love will answer everything
If you follow the Leader,
Love will answer everything,
If you follow the Leader.
When I go along the road,
I shall lift a heavy load.
I will carry a cross for you.
You will learn to carry it too
When you follow the Leader,
When you follow the Leader.
I am going to stretch My hands,
Reaching out to all the lands.
Can I really be a king?
Love’s the lord of everything,
When you follow the Leader,
When you follow the Leader
Love’s the lord of everything,
When you follow the Leader.