We have heard a joyful sound,
Jesus saves, Jesus saves;
Spread the gladness all around,
Bear the news to every land,
Climb the steeps and cross the waves,
Onward, ’tis our Lord’s command,
Jesus saves, Jesus saves.
Waft it on the rolling tide,
Jesus saves, Jesus saves;
Tell to sinners, far and wide,
Sing, ye islands of the sea.
Echo back, ye ocean caves,
Earth shall keep her jubilee,
Jesus saves, Jesus saves.
Sing above the battle’s strife,
Jesus saves, Jesus saves;
By His death and endless life,
Sing it softly through the gloom,
When the heart for mercy craves,
Sing in triumph o’er the tomb,
Jesus saves, Jesus saves.
Give the winds a mighty voice,
Jesus saves, Jesus saves;
Let the nations now rejoice,
Shout salvation full and free,
Highest hills and deepest caves,
This our song of victory,
Jesus saves, Jesus saves.