Father, help Your people in this world to build
Something of Your kingdom and to do Your will,
Lead us to discover partnership in love;
Bless our ways of sharing and our pride remove.
Lord of desk and altar, bind our lives in one,
That in work and worship love may set the tone.
Give us grace to listen, clarity of speech;
Make us truly thankful for the gifts of each.
Holy is the setting of each room and yard,
Lecture hall and kitchen, office, shop, and ward.
Holy is the rhythm of our working hours;
Hallow then our purpose, energy, and pow’rs.
Strengthen, Lord, for service hand and heart and brain;
Help us good relations daily to maintain.
Let the living presence of the servant Christ
Heighten our devotion, make our life a feast.