Arise, my soul, arise!
Stretch forth to things eternal
And hasten to the feet of your Redeemer God.
Though hid from mortal eyes,
He dwells in light supernal;
Yet worship Him in humbleness and call Him Lord.
Awaits you above;
Yet here He grants a foretaste of the feast
to come!
Rejoice, my soul, rejoice,
To heav地 lift up your voice:
Alleluia, alleluia, alleluia!
Now hear the harps of heav地!
Oh, hear the song victorious,
The never-ending anthem sounding
through the sky!
To mortals is not giv地
To join in strains so glorious;
our praises high!
He bought with His blood
The ransomed of God;
To Him be everlasting pow池 and victory.
And let the great amen
Resound through heav地 again.
Alleluia, alleluia, alleluia!