Safely through another week
God has brought us on our way;
Let us now a blessing seek,
Waiting in His courts today;
Day of all the week the best,
Emblem of eternal rest:
Emblem of eternal rest.
While we seek supplies of grace,
Thro’ the dear Redeemer’s name,
Show Thy reconciling face;
Take away the sin and shame:
From our worldly cares set free,
May we rest this day in Thee:
May we rest this day in Thee.
When the more shall bid us rise,
May we feel Thy presence near;
May Thy glory meet our eyes,
While we in Thy house appear:
Here afford us, Lord, a taste
Of our everlasting feast:
Of our everlasting feast.
May the gospel’s joyful sound
Conquer sinners, comfort saints;
Make the fruits of grace abound,
Bring relief to all complaints:
Thus may all our Sabbaths be,
Till we we rise to reign with Thee.