Christ, the Lord, all power possessing,
Parting, mounted heaven’s height,
Gracious hands outstretched in blessing,
Clouds received His from their sight.
Christ ascended, Christ ascended,
Christ ascended on the clouds.
(on the clouds)
Daniel views earth’s judgment hour,
Angels gathering open books.
God enthroned inflaming power
For His Son’s arrival looks.
Christ approaches, Christ approaches,
Christ approaches on the clouds.
(on the clouds)
Revelation’s word fulfilling,
Trumpet, voices pierce the air.
Saint and sinner fainting, thrilling,
Every eye behold Him there.
Christ is coming, Christ is coming,
Christ is coming on the clouds.
(on the clouds)