For all the saints
who from their labors rest,
Who thee by faith
before the world confessed.
Thy name, O Jesus,
be forever blest.
Alleluia!
Thou wast their Rock,
their Fortress and their Might;
Thou, Lord, their captain
in the well-fought fight;
Thou, in the darkness drear,
their one true light.
Alleluia!
O may Thy soldiers,
faithful, true, and bold,
Fight as the saints
who nobly fought of old,
And win with them
the victor’s crown of gold.
Alleluia!
And when the strife is fierce,
the warfare long,
Steals on the ear
the distant triumph song,
And hearts are brave again,
and arms are strong.
Alleluia!
From earth’s wide bounds,
from ocean’s farthest coast,
Thro’ gates of pearl
streams in the countless host,
Singing to Father,
Son, and Holy Ghost,
Alleluia!