Come, we that love the Lord,
And let our joys be known;
Join in a song with sweet accord,
And thus surround the throne,
And thus surround the throne.
We’re marching to Zion,
Beautiful, beautiful Zion;
We’re marching upward to Zion,
The beautiful city of God.
Let those refuse to sing
Who never knew our God;
But children of the heav’nly King,
But children of the heav’nly King
May speak their joys abroad,
May speak their joys abroad.
The hill of Zion yields
A thousand sacred sweets
Before we reach the heav’nly fields,
Before we reach the heav’nly fields
Or walk the golden streets,
Or walk the golden streets.
Then let our songs abound
And ev’ry tear be dry;
We’re marching thru Immanuel’s ground,
We’re marching thru Immanuel’s ground
To fairer worlds on high,
To fairer worlds on high.