Glorious things of thee are spoken,
Zion, city of our God;
He whose word cannot be broken
Formed thee for His own abode;
On the Rock of Ages founded,
What can shake thy sure repose?
With salvation’s wall surrounded,
Thou mayest smile at all thy foes.
See the streams of living waters
Springing from eternal love,
Well supply thy sons and daughters,
And all fear and want remove;
Who can faint when such a river
Ever flows their thirst to assuage?
Grace, which, like the Lord, the Giver,
Never fails from age to age.
Round each habitation hovering,
See the cloud and fire appear
For a glory and a covering,
Showing that the Lord is near;
Blest inhabitants of Zion,
Washed in the Redeemer’s blood;
Jesus, whom their souls rely on,
Makes them kings and priests to God.
Savior, if of Zion’s city
I, through grace, a member am,
Let the world deride or pity,
I will glory in Thy name;
Fading is the worldling’s pleasure,
All his boasted pomp and show;
Solid joys and lasting treasure
None but Zion’s children know.