Far away in the depths of my spirit tonight,
Rolls a melody sweeter than psalm;
In celestial like strains it unceasingly falls
O’er my soul like an infinite calm.
Peace! Peace! wonderful peace,
Coming down from the Father above;
Sweep over my spirit forever, I pray,
In fathomless billows of love.
What a treasure I have in this wonderful peace,
Buried deep in my inner most soul,
So secure that no power can mine it away,
While the years of eternity roll!
I believe when I rise to that city of peace,
Where the Author of peace I shall see,
That one strain of the song which the ransomed will sing,
In that heavenly kingdom will be-
Weary soul, without gladness or comfort or rest,
Passing down the rough pathway of time!
Make the Savior your friend ere the shadows grow dark;
O accept of this peace so sublime.