‘Tis the blessed hour of prayer, when our hearts lowly bend,
And we gather to Jesus, our Savior and Friend;
If we come to Him in faith, His protection to share,
What a balm for the weary! O how sweet to be there!
Blessed hour of prayer, Blessed hour of prayer,
‘Tis the blessed hour of prayer, when the Savior draws near,
With a tender compassion His children to hear;
When He tells us we may cast at His feet every care,
‘Tis the blessed hour of prayer, when the tempted and tried
To the Savior who loves them their sorrows confide;
With a sympathizing heart He removes every care;
‘Tis the blessed hour of prayer, trusting Him we believe,
That the blessings we’re needing we’ll surely receive;
In the fullness of this trust we shall lose every care;