Just when I need Him, Jesus is near,
Just when I falter, just when I fear;
Ready to help me, ready to cheer,
Just when I need Him most.
Just when I need Him most,
Jesus is near to comfort and cheer,
Just when I need Him most.
Just when I need Him, Jesus is true,
Never forsaking, all the way through,
Giving for burdens pleasures anew,
Just when I need Him most.
Just when I need Him most,
Jesus is near to comfort and cheer,
Just when I need Him most.
Just when I need Him, Jesus is strong,
Bearing my burdens all the day long;
For all my sorrow giving a song,
Just when I need Him most.
Just when I need Him most,
Jesus is near to comfort and cheer,
Just when I need Him most.
Just when I need Him, He is my all,
Answering when upon Him I call;
Tenderly watching lest I should fall,
Just when I need Him most.
Just when I need Him most,
Jesus is near to comfort and cheer,
Just when I need Him most.