O, for a faith that will not shrink,
Though pressed by many a foe,
That will not tremble on the brink of poverty,
Of poverty or woe; Of poverty or woe;
That will not murmur or complain
Beneath the chastening rod,
But in the hour of grief or pain, of grief or pain
Can lean upon its God; Can lean upon its God.
A faith that shines more bright and clear
When tempests rage without;
That when in danger knows no fear, knows of no fear,
In darkness feels no doubt; In darkness feels no doubt.
That bears unmoved the world’s dread frown,
Nor heeds its scornful smile;
That sin’s wild ocean cannot drown, no, cannot drown,
Nor its soft arts beguile; Nor its soft arts beguile.
Lord, give me such a faith as this,
And then, whate’er may come
I’ll taste, e’en here the hallowed bliss, the hallowed bliss
Of an eternal home; Of an eternal home.