Give of your best to the master,
Give of the strength of your youth;
Throw your soul’s fresh, glowing ardor
Into the battle for truth.
Jesus has set the example –
Dauntless was He, young and brave;
Give Him your loyal devotion,
Give Him the best that you have.
Give of your best to the master,
Give of the strength of your youth;
Clad in salvation’s full armor,
Join in the battle for truth.
Give of your best to the Master,
Give Him first place in your heart;
Give Him first place in your service,
Consecrate every part.
Give, and to you shall be given –
God His beloved Son gave;
Gratefully seeking to serve Him,
Give Him the best that you have.
Give of your best to the Master,
Naught else is worthy His love;
He gave Himself for your ransom,
Have up His glory above;
Laid down His life without murmur,
You from sin’s ruin to save;
Give Him your heart’s adoration,
Give Him the best that you have.