In the heart of Jesus there is love for you,
Love most pure and tender, love most deep and true;
Why should you be lonely, why for friendship sigh,
When the heart of Jesus has a full supply?
In the mind of Jesus there is thought for you,
Warm as summer sunshine, sweet as morning dew;
Why should you be fearful, why take anxious thought,
Since the mind of Jesus cares for those He bought?
In the field of Jesus there is work for you;
Such as even angels might rejoice to do;
Why stand idly sighing for some lifework grand,
While the field of Jesus seeks your reaping hand?
In the home of Jesus there’s a place for you;
Glorious, bright, and joyous, calm and peaceful too;
Why then, like a wanderer, roam with weary pace,
If the home of Jesus holds for you a place?