Watchman, tell us of the night what its signs of promise are.
Traveler, o’er yon mountain’s height, see that glory beaming star.
Watchman, does its beauteous ray aught of joy or hope foretell?
Traveler, yes; it brings the day, promised day of Israel.
Watchman, tell us of the night, higher yet that star ascends.
Traveler, blessedness and light, peace and truth its course portends.
Watchman, will its beams alone gild the spot that gave them birth?
Traveler, ages are its own; See it bursts o’er all the earth.
Watchman, tell us of the night, for the morning seems to dawn.
Traveler, darkness takes its flight, doubt and terror are withdrawn.
Watchman, let your wanderings cease; hasten to your quiet home.
Traveler, lo, the Prince of Peace, lo, the Son of God is come!