In times like these you need a Savior,
In times like these you need and anchor;
Be very sure, be very sure Your anchor holds and grips the Solid rock!
This Rock is Jesus, Yes, He’s the One;
This Rock is Jesus, The only One!
Be very sure, be very sure Your anchor holds and grips the Solid rock!
In times like these you need the Bible,
In times like these O be not idle;
Be very sure, be very sure Your anchor holds and grips the Solid rock!
This Rock is Jesus, Yes, He’s the One;
This Rock is Jesus, The only One!
Be very sure, be very sure Your anchor holds and grips the Solid rock!
In times like these I have a Savior,
In times like these I have an anchor
I’m very sure, be very sure Your anchor holds and grips the Solid rock!
This Rock is Jesus, Yes, He’s the One;
This Rock is Jesus, The only One!
I’m very sure, be very sure My anchor holds and grips the Solid rock!