Let every lamp be burning bright,
The darkest hour is nearing;
The darkest hour of earth’s long night,
Before the Lord’s appearing.
Then trim your lamps, my brethren dear,
Then trim your lamps with godly fear;
The Master’s coming draweth near,
Let every lamp be burning.
Though thousands calmly slumber on,
The last great message spurning,
We’ll rest our living faith upon
His promise of returning.
His word our lamp, His truth our guide,
We cannot be mistaken;
Though dangers rise on every side,
We shall not be forsaken.
Then let good works with faith appear,
To help the world around us;
Obedience bring the blessing near
When faith has firmly bound us.