O brother be faithful! soon Jesus will come,
For whom we have waited so long;
O, soon we shall enter our glorious home,
And join in the conqueror’s song.
O brother be faithful! for why should we prove
Unfaithful to Him who had shown
Such deep, such unbounded and infinite love
Who died to redeem us His own.
O brother be faithful! the city of gold,
Prepared for the good and the blest,
Is waiting its portals of pearl to unfold,
And welcome thee into thy rest.
Then, brother be faithful! not long shall we stay
In weariness here, and forlorn,
Time’s dark night of sorrow is wearing away,
We haste to the glorious morn.
O brother be faithful! He soon will descend,
Creation’s omnipotent King,
While legions of angels His chariot attend,
And palm wreaths, of victory bring.
O brother be faithful! and soon shalt thou hear
They Savior pronounce the glad word,
Well done, faithful servant, they title is clear,
To enter the joy of thy Lord.
O brother be faithful! eternity’s years
Shall tell for thy faithfulness now,
When bright smiles of gladness shall scatter thy tears,
A coronet gleam on thy brow.
O brother be faithful! the promise is sure,
That waits for the faithful and tried;
To reign with the ransomed, immortal and pure,
And ever with Jesus abide.