God of grace and God of glory,
On Thy people pour Thy power;
Now fulfill Thy church’s story,
Bring her bud to glorious flower.
Grant us wisdom, grant us courage,
For the facing of this hour.
Lo, the hosts of evil round us
Scorn Thy Christ, assail His ways;
From the fears that long have bound us
Free our hearts to faith and praise.
Grant us wisdom, grant us courage,
For the facing of this hour.
Cure Thy children’s warring madness,
Bend our pride to Thy control;
Shame our wanton selfish gladness
Rich in goods and poor in soul.
Grant us wisdom, grant us courage,
Lest we miss Thy kingdom’s goal.
Set our feet on lofty places,
Gird our lives that they may be
Armored with all Christ-like graces
In the fight to set all free.
Grant us wisdom, grant us courage,
That we fail not man nor Thee.