God is here as we his people
meet to offer praise and prayer,
may we find in fuller measure
what it is in Christ we share.
Here, as in the world around us,
all our varied skills and arts
wait the coming of his Spirit
into open minds and hearts.
Here are symbols to remind us
of our lifelong need of grace;
here are table, font and pulpit;
here the Word has central place.
Here in honesty of preaching,
here in silence, as in speech,
here in newness and renewal,
God the Spirit comes to each.
Here our children find a welcome
in the Shepherd’s flock and fold.
Here, as bread and wine are taken,
Christ sustains us, as of old.
Here the servants of the Servant
seek in worship to explore
what it means in daily living
to believe and to adore.
Lord of all, Church and Kingdom,
in an age of change and doubt,
keep us faithful to the Gospel,
help us work your purpose out.
Here, in this day’s dedication,
all we have to give, receive:
we, who cannot live without you,
we adore you! We believe!