On Jordan’s stormy banks I stand,
And cast a wishful eye
To Canaan’s fair and happy land,
Where my possessions lie.
I am bound for the promised land,
I am bound for the promised land;
O who will come and go with me?
O’er all those wide extended plain
Shines one eternal day;
There, Christ, the Sun, for ever reigns,
And scatters night away.
I am bound for the promised land,
O who will come and go with me?
I am bound for the promised land.
When shall I reach that happy place,
And be forever blest?
When shall I see my Father’s face,
And in His kingdom rest?
I am bound for the promised land,
O who will come and go with me?
I am bound for the promised land.
Filled with delight, my raptured soul
Would here no longer stay;
Though Jordan’s waves around me roll,
Fearless I’d launch away.
I am bound for the promised land,
I am bound for the promised land;
O who will come and go with me?
I am bound for the promised land.