Let us sing a song that will cheer us by the way,
In a little while we’re going home.
For the night will end in the everlasting day,
In a little while, In a little while,
We shall cross the billow’s foam;
We shall meet at last, When the stormy winds are past,
In a little while we’re going home.
We will do the work that our hands may find to do,
And the grace of God will our daily strength renew,
In a little while we’re going home.
We will smooth the path for some weary, wayworn feet,
And may loving hearts spread around an influence sweet!
In a little while we’re going home.
There’s a rest beyond, there’s relief from every care,
In a little while we’re going home;
And no tears shall fall in that city bright and fair,
In a little while we’re going home.