Though I speak with tongues of men and angels,
Though I have the prophet’s gift,
Though I hold the keys to hidden knowledge,
Though my faith can mountains shift;
Without love I am no better,
Without love it’s all for naught;
Lord, You spent Your life in loving others:
What this means I would be taught.
Love is patient, knows no envy,
Never gloats when others sin;
Love is never glad to see injustice,
Always wants the truth to win.
There’s no end to love’s endurance,
There’s no test it cannot face;
Lord, You spent Your life in loving others:
I shall fail without Your grace.
Though there’ll be an end to hidden knowledge,
Visions, raptures, prophecy:
Faith and hope and love shall last forever,
Love the greatest of the three.
Without love I am no better,
Without love it’s all for naught;
Lord, You gave Your life in saving others:
What this means I would be taught.